[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "The ..... is the most treasured asset of an organization and must be cherished.",
        "correct": "customer"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "The customer is the most valuable ..... of the organization and it must be cherished",
        "correct": "asset"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Belief, norms, values and customs shapes the (social-cultural) ..... environment",
        "correct": "Business"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "..... (Belief, values) is an element of social environment",
        "correct": "Norms"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "..... environment deals with gift of nature or natural resources of a country.",
        "correct": "Natural"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Water venture is a good example of ..... proprietorship business.",
        "correct": "Sole"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Opportunity dwell in ..... business environment",
        "correct": "economic"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Ineffective control measure is an example of cause of business .....",
        "correct": "failure"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Premature expansion is an example of Cause of business .....",
        "correct": "Failure"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Decline in production is an example of Symptoms of business .....",
        "correct": "Failure"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Feasibility study determines the ..... (liability, Workability) of an intended business",
        "correct": "Profitability"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Equity finance is produced by the .....",
        "correct": "Entrepreneur"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Identify four types of entrepreneurs:",
        "statements": [
            "(I) Fabian.",
            "(II) .....",
            "(III) Innovative",
            "(IV) Imitative"
        ],
        "correct": "Drone"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Money use by an entrepreneur to purchase machines, tools and equipment is called .....",
        "correct": "Capital"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "An entrepreneur who introduce new product that has never been known into the market is called .....",
        "correct": "Innovator"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "..... and Employment (apprenticeship) are expected to be fulfill before an entrepreneur start a venture.",
        "correct": "Education"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "In the French concept entrepreneur means ..... *\"to undertake\"*.",
        "correct": "Entreprende"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "..... are individuals who carry out entrepreneurship activities to build business empires.",
        "correct": "Entrepreneurs"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "..... is the process and activities by which corporate organization behave entrepreneurially.",
        "correct": "Entrepreneurship"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "The *2nd Ps* of marketing is called .....",
        "correct": "Price"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "..... means *Manufacturing Association of Nigeria*.",
        "correct": "MAN"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "..... means *National Directorate of Employment*.",
        "correct": "NDE"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "..... means *Small and Medium Enterprise Development Agency of Nigeria*.",
        "correct": "SMEDAN"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "..... means *Corruption Practice Commission*.",
        "correct": "CPC"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "..... means *Cooperate Affairs Commission*.",
        "correct": "CAC"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "..... is important because it creates utility and promotes economic growth and development.",
        "correct": "Entrepreneurship"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "An entrepreneur uses the technique of ..... analysis to evaluate *Strength Weakness Opportunity Threats*",
        "correct": "SWOT"
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "In SWOT analysis, T stands for .....",
        "correct": "Threats"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "For business organization to become a legal entity it has to be registered with .....",
        "correct": "CAC"
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "..... is considered as *short term/medium* source of business finance.",
        "correct": "Leasing"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "Of all forms of businesses ..... companies is the most complex in formation and operation.",
        "correct": "Cooperation"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "..... is investment entirely in different line of business.",
        "correct": "Diversification"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "The Owner of a ..... company is subjected to double taxation",
        "correct": "Cooperative"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "Wrong choice of business line is an example of ..... of business failure",
        "correct": "Cause"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "The process of dividing a total market into smaller units is called .....",
        "correct": "Segmentation"
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "..... agencies (Transportation services, Market Research firm, Warehousing, Communication) is a marketing facilitator.",
        "correct": "Advertising"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "..... is the *6th P* of marketing mix.",
        "correct": "Process"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "..... condition *(Demographic factors, behavioral pattern, physical characteristics)* is a technique used in market segmentation.",
        "correct": "Market"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "..... insurance covers the damage occurred to the products only.",
        "correct": "Product"
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "..... partner is limited only to his/her level of investment in the business.",
        "correct": "Limited"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "*_Political/Legal business environment_* operates on the principles of ..... control.",
        "correct": "Democratic"
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "One of the features of ..... proprietorship is that, the liabilities of the amount they invested in the business.",
        "correct": "Sole"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "An entrepreneur who adopts changes only when it is successful in other organizations is called .....",
        "correct": "Fabian"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "*Lack of capital and Problem of succession* are problems facing Nigerian .....",
        "correct": "Entrepreneurs"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "The *first 4 Ps* of marketing mix are: ",
        "statements": [
            "(1) Product",
            "(2) Price",
            "(3) Place",
            "(4) ....."
        ],
        "correct": "Promotion"
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "*Company Limited by Shares and Company Limited by .....* are two types of companies.",
        "correct": "Guarantee"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "*Company Limited by .....* are formed usually for charitable, educational and religious purpose.",
        "correct": "Guarantee"
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "*Public company (plc)*, its ownership ranges from seven(7) to .....",
        "correct": "Infinity"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "Private and Public are two types of companies limited by .....",
        "correct": "Shares"
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "Partnership is a form of business organized and owned by two or more persons by ..... arrangement.",
        "correct": "Voluntary"
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "In partnership, the relationship is guided by partnership .....",
        "correct": "DEEDS"
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "..... limited, its article of association restrict the right to transfer its shares.",
        "correct": "Private"
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "Financial analysis helps in testing the ..... and other financial benefits of the business.",
        "correct": "Fund"
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "According to _Kayode O. Fasuwa_ there are ..... types of entrepreneurs.",
        "correct": "4"
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "Element of marketing is also known as ..... Mix",
        "correct": "Marketing"
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "question": "The ..... environment study the statistics of people living in a particular geographical setting.",
        "correct": "Demographic"
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "question": "The Demographic environment study statistics of people living in a particular ..... setting",
        "correct": "Geographical"
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "question": "..... business environment is one in which an entrepreneur assesses availability and cost of raw materials.",
        "correct": "Natural"
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "question": "The reward an entrepreneur gets for bearing risk involved in the enterprise is ..... which is highly uncertain.",
        "correct": "Profit"
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "question": "The reward an entrepreneur gets for bearing risk involved in the enterprise is profit which is highly .....",
        "correct": "Uncertain"
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "question": "..... decision ensures prudent spending",
        "correct": "Management"
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "question": "..... directs human and material resources to achieve his business objectives",
        "correct": "Entrepreneur"
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "question": "..... is any activity or set of activities that is geared towards a profitable goal",
        "correct": "Business"
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "question": "*Cars and Jewelries* are the examples of ..... goods",
        "correct": "Specialty"
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "question": "Market ..... is the management that concerns planning and controlling the company financial resources.",
        "correct": "Study"
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "question": "..... is a marketing communication put in place to make the customers aware of the products.",
        "correct": "Promotion"
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "question": "The manager should be tolerant of learning .....",
        "correct": "Errors"
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "question": "Corporation company is also known as ..... company.",
        "correct": "Registered"
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "question": "The shares are often bought and sold at in the ..... market (or stock market or open market).",
        "correct": "Capital"
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "question": "..... is a certificate issued by a company promising to pay back borrowed money at a fixed rate of interest on a specified date.",
        "correct": "Bond"
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "question": "..... is the selling out of shares to the public or companies in order to generate funds to finance the current business.",
        "correct": "Stock"
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "question": "*Financial study and Market study* (environmental study, socio-economic study, technical study, legal study, general description) are the two components of ..... study.",
        "correct": "feasibility"
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "question": "Formal transfers of share certificates, titles is normally handled by .....",
        "correct": "Shareholders"
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "question": "*Private Limited Liability Company* limits membership between two to .....",
        "correct": "50"
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "question": "An ..... must have leadership ability to succeed.",
        "correct": "Entrepreneur"
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "question": "Sole ..... entrepreneur essentially work alone and if needed at all, employs a few employees.",
        "correct": "Proprietor"
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "question": "..... company is a body authorized by law to act as a private person and legally endowed with various rights and duties, including the right of succession.",
        "correct": "Cooperation"
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "question": "Leasing is considered as ..... source of business",
        "options": {
            "a": "short",
            "b": "medium",
            "c": "long",
            "d": "infinity"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "question": "An amount of money paid by an entrepreneur to insurance company is called",
        "options": {
            "a": "premium",
            "b": "legal tender",
            "c": "promissory",
            "d": "equity"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "question": "Natural environment deals with .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "forest resources",
            "b": "agricultural resources",
            "c": "mineral resources",
            "d": "all of the above"
        },
        "correct": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "question": "A process of dividing a total market into smaller units is called .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "segmentation",
            "b": "sedimentation",
            "c": "Homogeneous",
            "d": "psycho graphic"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "question": "One of the merits of corporation is .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "profit",
            "b": "competency",
            "c": "growing concern",
            "d": "change"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "question": "..... is among the types of entrepreneurs developed by behavioural scientists.",
        "options": {
            "a": "drone",
            "b": "innovator",
            "c": "Fabian",
            "d": "inventor"
        },
        "correct": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "question": "Increase in product acceptance is ..... in the business.",
        "options": {
            "a": "weakness",
            "b": "strength",
            "c": "profit",
            "d": "opportunity"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "question": "Feasibility report comprise the following except:",
        "options": {
            "a": "financial",
            "b": "technical",
            "c": "equity",
            "d": "marketing"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "question": "Entrepreneurs set their own goals rather than having them set by their .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "Subordinates",
            "b": "Directors",
            "c": "Managers",
            "d": "Bosses"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "question": "Machines and tools are examples of .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "fixed asset",
            "b": "current asset",
            "c": "liability",
            "d": "debenture"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "question": "The ownership public company ranges from",
        "options": {
            "a": "7 to infinity",
            "b": "7 to 100",
            "c": "7 to 50",
            "d": "many"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "question": "..... is not one of the marketing facilitators.",
        "options": {
            "a": "warehouse",
            "b": "advertising",
            "c": "selling",
            "d": "market"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "question": "A good leader must develop new insatiable ..... and break new grounds and develop desire for knowledge",
        "options": {
            "a": "ideas",
            "b": "skills",
            "c": "methods",
            "d": "strategies"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "question": "In *SWOT analysis*, increases in product acceptance is a/an .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "opportunities",
            "b": "breaker",
            "c": "strength",
            "d": "profit"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "question": "..... uses the techniques of *SWOT analysis* to test his business ideas",
        "options": {
            "a": "Marketers",
            "b": "entrepreneur",
            "c": "inventor",
            "d": "motivator"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "question": "..... is one of the components of financial planning",
        "options": {
            "a": "book keeping",
            "b": "financial forecasting",
            "c": "financial report",
            "d": "internal control"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "question": ".....  is the selling out of shares to the public in order to generate funds to finance the business",
        "options": {
            "a": "bonds",
            "b": "trade credit",
            "c": "stock",
            "d": "stack"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "question": "According to *Kayode O. Fasuwa*, there are ..... types of entrepreneurs.",
        "options": {
            "a": "7",
            "b": "5",
            "c": "6",
            "d": "4"
        },
        "correct": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "question": "The stage of rapid market acceptance and substantial profit improvement in the product life cycle is .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "decline stage",
            "b": "growth",
            "c": "maturity",
            "d": "introduction"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "question": "Cooperative societies was first establish in the year",
        "options": {
            "a": "1944",
            "b": "1804",
            "c": "1844",
            "d": "1854"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "question": "The importance of financial planning is .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "To take improper decision",
            "b": "minimize profit",
            "c": "maximize profit",
            "d": "saving decision"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "question": "Availability of knowledgeable and qualified financial manager lead to .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "Good profit maximization",
            "b": "maximize cost",
            "c": "effective management",
            "d": "squandering"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "question": "Mention 2 types of capital required for setting up a business are:",
        "options": {
            "a": "Fixed and working capital",
            "b": "Fixed and debenture capital",
            "c": "Fixed and equity capital",
            "d": "investment and working capital"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "question": "..... is the partner that is not involved in the daily running of business",
        "options": {
            "a": "Nominal",
            "b": "Dormant",
            "c": "Limited",
            "d": "Active"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "question": "..... are characterized by refusal to adopt opportunities to make changes in production even at the cost of reduced returns.",
        "options": {
            "a": "drone entrepreneur",
            "b": "Fabian entrepreneur",
            "c": "Imitative entrepreneur",
            "d": "challengers"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "question": "A good feasibility report must comprise the following except:",
        "options": {
            "a": "Marketing",
            "b": "Financial",
            "c": "Equity",
            "d": "Technological"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "question": "A good feasibility report must comprise the following except:",
        "options": {
            "a": "marketing",
            "b": "technical",
            "c": "resources",
            "d": "financial"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "question": "Project goes with conception of .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "information",
            "b": "view",
            "c": "forecasting",
            "d": "ideas"
        },
        "correct": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "question": "Business failure is a situation where the business cannot meet it obligations",
        "options": {
            "a": "financial obligations",
            "b": "peak",
            "c": "maximum profit",
            "d": "management decision"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "question": "Equity finance is provided by the .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "bank",
            "b": "friends",
            "c": "family",
            "d": "entrepreneur"
        },
        "correct": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "question": "..... sources are the corporate financial institutions, such as capital market and Nigerian Industrial bank",
        "options": {
            "a": "external",
            "b": "institutional",
            "c": "informal",
            "d": "private"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "question": "Encouraging economic growth and development is one of an entrepreneurship .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "rewards",
            "b": "characteristics",
            "c": "contribution",
            "d": "functions"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "question": "An insurance contract must meet some conditions which includes:",
        "options": {
            "a": "offer",
            "b": "capacity",
            "c": "acceptance",
            "d": "all"
        },
        "correct": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "question": "One of these is not a component of financial management",
        "options": {
            "a": "financial report",
            "b": "bank reconciliation",
            "c": "taxation",
            "d": "internet control"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "question": "The following are functions of marketing except:",
        "options": {
            "a": "product development",
            "b": "distribution",
            "c": "management services",
            "d": "Promotion of goods and services"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "question": "In partnership, the ..... is guided by a partnership deed.",
        "options": {
            "a": "business",
            "b": "conditions",
            "c": "relationship",
            "d": "bonds"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "question": "The owners of a corporation company are subjected to .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "double income",
            "b": "project",
            "c": "double taxation",
            "d": "investment"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "question": "In feasibility study, the technique of SWOT analysis are used to test .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "the financial planning",
            "b": "business ideas",
            "c": "the opportunities",
            "d": "the strength"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "question": "Business failure is caused by one of the following:",
        "options": {
            "a": "Political stability",
            "b": "laziness",
            "c": "prudent spending",
            "d": "none of the above"
        },
        "correct": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "question": "All are symptoms of Business failure except:",
        "options": {
            "a": "Declining working capital",
            "b": "reduce in profit",
            "c": "loosing of Key staff",
            "d": "declining demand"
        },
        "correct": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "question": "Plants and machines, buildings, vehicles are the major ..... needed for successful operation of business",
        "options": {
            "a": "technical input",
            "b": "financial feasibility",
            "c": "marketing feasibility",
            "d": "technical output"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "question": "The entrepreneur should also know the needs of the staff, their hopes and aspirations in the levels at the .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "organization",
            "b": "company",
            "c": "workplace",
            "d": "market place"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "question": "In Taiwan, they employ more than ..... of jobs in production activities and they account for ..... of export.",
        "options": {
            "a": "70% and 60%",
            "b": "70% and 75%",
            "c": "50% and 70%",
            "d": "40% and 70%"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "question": "..... is the period that the product has achieved acceptance by most of the potential buyers.",
        "options": {
            "a": "maturity",
            "b": "decline",
            "c": "instructions",
            "d": "growth"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "question": "..... are products that consumers need but not willing to spend much time shopping for.",
        "options": {
            "a": "shopping goods",
            "b": "specialty goods",
            "c": "convenience goods",
            "d": "consumers goods"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "question": "Many business have failed in recent times not because of lack of finance or management but lack of:",
        "options": {
            "a": "accountability",
            "b": "leadership style",
            "c": "poor feasibility study",
            "d": "administration"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "question": "..... Direct human and material resources in other to achieve their business objectives.",
        "options": {
            "a": "entrepreneurs",
            "b": "innovators",
            "c": "sole operators",
            "d": "active partners"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "question": "..... is anything that can be offered to market for attention, acquisition, use or consumption.",
        "options": {
            "a": "convenience goods",
            "b": "product",
            "c": "goods",
            "d": "service"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "question": "The conception of ideas is translated into .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "project",
            "b": "pre-feasibility",
            "c": "feasibility report",
            "d": "ventures"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "question": "In united state there are about ..... *SME*s employing more than ..... of private work force.",
        "options": {
            "a": "2.1 million and 50%",
            "b": "23 million and 30%",
            "c": "23 million and 50%",
            "d": "15 million and 50%"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "question": "Inefficiency, ineffectiveness and organizational conflicts are often blamed on ..... communication",
        "options": {
            "a": "informal and formal communication",
            "b": "vertical and horizontal",
            "c": "communication breakdown",
            "d": "poor performance level"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "question": "The aim of a venture is to create ..... and .....",
        "options": {
            "a": "profit and good will",
            "b": "wealth and personality",
            "c": "wealth and profit",
            "d": "profit and loss"
        },
        "correct": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "question": "Risk is undertaken by entrepreneur consciously or unconsciously.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "question": "Availability of qualified financial manager leads to finance control and spendthrift.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "question": "Powerful idea is the backbone of every surviving human organization.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "question": "Innovation is considered to be the strategic tool of business.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "question": "Feasibility studies are not important when establishing sole proprietorship business.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "question": "Marketing is the same as buying and selling of goods and services.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "question": "Warehousing is the development of ways or techniques of making or doing things",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "question": "Banned on the use of motorcycles in Maiduguri has no effect on other businesses",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "question": "Insurance is the non transfer of risks from one entity to another",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "question": "The entrepreneur brings about searches for change, respond to it and exploit opportunity",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "question": "The success or failure of one man business depends on the owners inability to manage the business effectively.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "question": "In business context *\"enterprende\"* means to undertake.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "question": "The entrepreneur is someone who perceived opportunities were others succeeds.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "question": "Business is any undertaking created for the purpose of creating awareness.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "question": "A company can incorporate by shares, rules and by guarantee.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "question": "The belief, norms and values shapes the Natural environment of the business.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "question": "Lack of fund to undertake promotion is one of the threats in business.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "question": "Mutability is a feature of the business environment",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "question": "In partnership business, mobilization of capital is one of the advantages.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "question": "There is no difference between tangible and non-physical product.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "question": "Business failure is a situation where the business cannot meet its maximum profit",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "question": "One of the characteristic of an entrepreneur is the desire for dependence",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "question": "One of the problems of Nigerian entrepreneurs is income generation.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "question": "Entrepreneurship is a reality, concept topic and theory",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "question": "Drone entrepreneur is innovative, creative and initiative.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 155,
        "question": "National investment promotion commission is in charge of registration of business names, articles of association and legal documents.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "question": "Seminars organized by government agencies, universities or even private consultants are example of formal search for investment opportunities.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 157,
        "question": "At pre-feasibility, survey is made to gather the final information about the generated idea or project.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 158,
        "question": "In market feasibility, when the market is not adequate, investment in the business would be worthwhile.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 159,
        "question": "The reward an entrepreneur gets for bearing risks involved in the enterprise is profit which is highly uncertain.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 160,
        "question": "The owner of a corporation is subjected to double taxation.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 161,
        "question": "A manager needs to possess distinct qualification in terms of risk bearing ability.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "question": "Working capital is the heart of business and it is a sustaining factor in ventures.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 163,
        "question": "Freedom to select product, service, location and market is advantages of buying an existing business.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 164,
        "question": "Inadequate capital and incompetent management are causes of business failure.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 165,
        "question": "Nigerian population is skewed towards maturity and saturation.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 166,
        "question": "Co-operative company, the ownership investment is transferable from one individual to the other.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 167,
        "question": "Convenience goods are products that customers need but willing to spend much time shopping for.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 168,
        "question": "Specialty goods are the goods, the customers really want and will make a special effort to buy.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 169,
        "question": "Growth stage in product life cycle, is the period that the product has achieved acceptance by most of the potential buyers.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 170,
        "question": "Price is an equilibrating factor in the market place harmonizing the demand in the market with supply.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 171,
        "question": "Efficiency is a form of economy since its essence is the conservation of energy, time and space.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 172,
        "question": "An *innovating entrepreneur* is the one who introduces new goods, inaugurates new methods of production and discovers new market.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 173,
        "question": "Private company ana partnership are two types of companies limited by shares",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 174,
        "question": "Limited partner is not allowed to take part in the management of the partnership business.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 175,
        "question": "The written agreement is particularly more undesirable in future event",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 176,
        "question": "Financial planning enables the entrepreneur to source funds at maximum cost.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 177,
        "question": "Transportation service is a marketing facilitator",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 178,
        "question": "Planning, organizing, directing and controlling are not element of management",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 179,
        "question": "The death of a sole proprietor often means the end of the enterprise.",
        "options": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correct": "a"
    }
]